Guide to the Yehuda Amichai Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Journals, 1954-1998; Series IV; 3.09; (8 boxes)
  - Journals, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 1471-1473)
  - Journals, 1965-1966 (Box 43, Folder 1474-1481)
  - Journals, 1966-1967 (Box 43, Folder 1482-1487)
  - Journals, 1967-1969 (Box 44, Folder 1488-1495)
  - Journals, 1970-1972 (Box 44, Folder 1496-1503)
  - Journals, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 1504)
  - Journals, 1972-1976 (Box 45, Folder 1505-1512)
  - Journals, 1976-1978 (Box 45, Folder 1513-1516)
  - Journals, 1978-1982 (Box 46, Folder 1517-1524)
  - Journals, 1982-1983 (Box 46, Folder 1525-1527)
  - Journals, 1983-1986 (Box 47, Folder 1528-1535)
  - Journals, 1987-1990 (Box 47, Folder 1536-1539)
  - Journals, 1990-1992 (Box 48, Folder 1540-1547)
  - Journals, 1992-1998, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1548-1550)
- Photographs, 1929-1999; Series V; 1.05; (3 boxes)
  Series V, Photographs, is organized into four subseries: Yehuda Amichai, Events and Trips, Other People, and Other.
  - YEHUDA AMICHAI
    - Yehuda Amichai Alone
      - Portraits and snapshots, 1944-1996, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1551-1553)
        Includes photograph by Layle Silbert
    - Yehuda Amichai with Others
      - Family, 1929-1991, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1554-1555)
        Includes photograph by Thomas Simmons
      - Hannover, Ruth, 1933 Oct (Box 49, Folder 1556)
      - Lenz, Siegfried, [1991] (Box 49, Folder 1557)
        Photograph by B. Keren
      - Matlin, Marlee, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 1558)
        Photographs by Thomas Victor
      - Müller, Karlheinz, [1990s] (Box 49, Folder 1559)
      - Paz, Octavio, 1971, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1560)
      - Pickering, Thomas R., 1986 (Box 49, Folder 1561)
      - Popa, Vasko, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 1562)
        With unidentified third party
      - Sassoon, Raymond, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 1563)
      - Scholem, Gershom Gerhard, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1564)
      - Schultz, ----, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1565)
      - Shalev, Meir, [1990s] (Box 49, Folder 1566)
      - Shiraishi, Kazuko, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 1567)
      - Solotaroff, Ted, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1568)
      - Swados, Elizabeth, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1569)
      - Voznesenski, Andrei, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 1570)
      - Wieseltier, Leon, [1990s] (Box 49, Folder 1571)
      - Yehoshua, [Abraham?] B., n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1572)
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1573)
    - Groups
      - First grade class, Würzburg, Germany, 1930 (Box 49, Folder 1574)
      - Others, 1967-1997, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1575)
        With Robert Frost, Ted Hughes, Teddy Kollek, Octavio Paz and others
  - EVENTS AND TRIPS
    - Bellagio, Italy, [1980s] (Box 49, Folder 1576)
    - Bialik Prize, Tel Aviv, Israel, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1577)
    - Cairo, Egypt, [1994-1995] (Box 49, Folder 1578)
    - Edinburgh, Scotland and [Wales?], [1990s] (Box 49, Folder 1579)
    - Honorary degree, Ben-Gurion University of the Negev, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 1580)
    - Honorary degree, Hebrew Union College, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 1581)
    - Honorary degree, Hebrew University, [1990s] (Box 49, Folder 1582)
    - International Poetry Festival, Library of Congress, Washington D.C., 1970 (Box 49, Folder 1583)
    - Israel Prize, Jeruslaem, Israel, 1982, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1584)
      With Zbigniew Herbert and others
    - [Israeli Museum, Jerusalem?], 1990 (Box 49, Folder 1585)
      With Teddy Kollek
    - Jerusalem 3000 Years, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 1586)
    - Jerusalem Prize, Jerusalem, Israel, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 1587)
      With J.M. Coetzee and others
    - Poetry International Rotterdam, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 1588)
      With Breyten Breytenbach
    - Reading, Haifu, Israel, 1988 Feb 29 (Box 49, Folder 1589)
    - Reading, Jerusalem, Israel, [1990s] (Box 49, Folder 1590)
    - Reading, München, Germany, 1998 Mar (Box 49, Folder 1591)
    - Reading tour, Bankok, Thailand, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 1592)
    - Reading tour, Bombay and New Dehli, India, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 1593-1595)
    - Reading tour, China, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 1596-1597)
    - Reading tour, Tokyo and Kyoto, Japan, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 1598-1600)
    - Spoleto Festival, Spoleto, Italy, [1966?] (Box 50, Folder 1601)
      With John Berryman and Octavio Paz
    - Struga Poetry Festival and "The Golden Wreath" award, Struga, Macedonia, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 1602)
    - Tel-Aviv Award, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1603)
    - White House reception, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 1604)
      With Pat Nixon
    - Würzburg, Germany, [1990s] (Box 50, Folder 1605)
      With [Karlheinz] Müller and unidentified others
    - Others, 1963, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1606)
      With Yitshak Navon
      Includes photograph by Shlomo Lavie
  - OTHER PEOPLE
    - Amichai, Chana, 1960, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1607)
    - Amichai, David, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 1608)
      See also: Hughes, Carol, Box 51, folder 1611
    - Amichai, Emanuella, 1983-1995 (Box 51, Folder 1609)
    - [Grünberger, Morti?], n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1610)
    - Hughes, Carol, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 1611)
      With David Amichai
    - Hughes, Ted, 1967, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 1612)
      With Alan Sillitoe and Chana Amichai
    - Ma, Gao Ming, 1996 Oct 12 (Box 51, Folder 1613)
    - ----, Sophia Ruth, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 1614)
    - Gym class pupils, 1946 (Box 51, Folder 1614a)
    - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1615)
  - OTHER
    - Artist's print of tree, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 1616)
    - Bookseller's window (Box 51, Folder 1617)
    - Drawing for a poem, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1618)
    - Dylan Thomas' house, Wales, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1619)
    - Jewish tombstone, Würzburg, Germany, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1620)
    - Printed version of Amichai's "Forgetting Someone" on streetcar, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1621)
    - Production of "Bells and Trains", 1971 (Box 51, Folder 1622)
    - Production of "Noah," Hebrew University, Jerusalem, [1960s] (Box 51, Folder 1623)
    - Publicity for reading at San Diego State University, n.y. Mar 7 (Box 51, Folder 1624)
    - Synagogue and Jewish House, Plovdiv, Bulgaria (Box 51, Folder 1625)
    - Unidentified cat, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1626)
    - Unidentified room, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1626a)
    - Yehuda Amicha's home and Yemin Moshe, Jerusalem, Israel, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 1627)
    - Empty photograph envelopes and folders, 1991, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1628-1629)
- Printed Materials, 1950-1999; Series VI; 8.55; (21 boxes)
  Series VI, Printed Materials, is organized into eleven subseries: Announcements; Awards; Bibliographies; Brochures and Promotional Material; Business Cards; Catalogs; Clippings; Conference and Event Material; Periodicals; Teaching Guides; and Other Material.
  - ANNOUNCEMENTS
    - Appearances by Yehuda Amichai, 1966-1998, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1630-1633)
    - Other events, 1973-1998 (Box 52, Folder 1634)
  - AWARDS
    - Ben-Gurion University of the Negev honorary degree, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 1635)
    - Biauk Prize, 1976 Apr 29 (Box 52, Folder 1636)
    - Israel Prize, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 1637)
      Includes letter from Israel Prize
    - Jerusalem 3000, 1996 Jan 17 (Box 52, Folder 1638)
    - Kulturpreis der Stadt Würzburg, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 1639)
    - Lions International, 1997 May 15 (Box 52, Folder 1640)
    - Literary Olympics, Inc., 1992 (Box 52, Folder 1641)
    - Municipality of Jerusalem citation, 1996 Jan 17
    - Struga Poetry Festival, Macedonia, Golden Wreath, 1995
    - Universitat Tel-Aviv honorary degree, 1995 May 21 (Box 52, Folder 1642)
    - Universitat Tel-Aviv honorary degree, 1996 May 12 (Box 52, Folder 1643-1644)
    - Others, 1967-1996, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1645)
  - BIBLIOGRAPHIES
    - A Check List of Israeli Literature in English, 1976-1999 (Box 52, Folder 1646-1647)
    - Israel Publishers and Authors and their Boooks on the World Publishing Scene, 1980, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1648)
    - [On Yehuda Amichai], 1974-1976, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1649)
  - BROCHURES AND PROMOTIONAL MATERIAL
    - B'nai B'rith Lecture Bureau, 1978-1995 (Box 52, Folder 1650)
    - Midpeninsula Free University, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 1651-1652)
    - Palmach, 1989, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 1653)
    - Plovdiv, Bulgaria, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1654)
    - Spoleto, Italy, 1967, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1655)
    - Others, 1967-1997, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1656-1662)
  - BUSINESS CARDS
    - Amichai, Yehuda, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1663)
    - Others, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1664-1665)
    - Others, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1666-1667)
  - CATALOGS
    - Jewish Publication Society of America, 1983-1984 (Box 54, Folder 1668)
    - Piper, 1990, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 1669)
    - Sefarim, 1985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 1670)
    - Sheep Meadow Press, 1993, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 1671)
    - Other, 1980-1995, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1672-1673)
  - CLIPPINGS
    - Arabic, 1990, n.d.
    - Chinese, 1993, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1674)
    - Croatian, n.d.
    - Czech, 1998 May 20 (Box 54, Folder 1675)
    - Dutch, 1978-1995, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1676)
    - English, 1966-1993, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1677-1682)
    - English, 1993-1999, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1683-1685)
    - French, 1988-1994, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1686)
    - German, 1969-1998, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1687-1691)
    - Hebrew, 1958-1999, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1692-1696)
    - Hungarian, 1968 Apr 12 (Box 55, Folder 1697)
    - Italian, 1988-1995, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1698)
    - Japanese, 1993, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1699)
    - Macedonian, 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 1700)
    - Romanian, 1969-1987, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1701)
    - Russian, 1993
    - Spanish, 1970-1997, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1702)
    - Swedish, 1988-1991
    - Unidentified
      - Stored in: Oversize, Box 90, folder 2125, n.d.
  - CONFERENCE AND EVENT MATERIAL
    - Bicentennial Intercultural Fesitval of the Performing Arts, 1987-1989 (Box 56, Folder 1703)
    - Else-Lasker Schüler Forum, 1993-1995 (Box 56, Folder 1704)
    - Festival di Spoleto, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 1705)
    - Festival Internacional de Poesia, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 1706)
    - Geraldine R. Dodge Poetry Festival, 1996 Sep (Box 56, Folder 1707)
    - Give Peace a Chance, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 1708)
    - The Hay Festival, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 1709)
    - International Conference for Translators of Hebrew Literature, 1994 Jan (Box 56, Folder 1710)
    - International Festival of Poetry, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 1711)
    - International PEN Congresses, 1975-1992 (Box 56, Folder 1712-1714)
    - International Poetry Days in Malmö, 1991 May (Box 56, Folder 1715)
    - International Poetry Festival, 1970 Apr (Box 56, Folder 1716)
    - International Poets' Festival, 1995 Mar (Box 56, Folder 1717)
    - International Writers' Conference, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 1718)
    - Israel Festival, Jerusalem, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 1719)
    - Jerusalem Poetry Festival, 1990-1994 (Box 56, Folder 1720-1721)
    - Jerusalem Poetry Festival, 1990-1994 (Box 57, Folder 1722-1723)
    - Poetry Center of the 92nd Street YM-YWHA (New York, N.Y.), 1986-1998 (Box 57, Folder 1724)
    - Poetry International '67, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 1725)
    - Poetry International Rotterdam, 1970-1995, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1726-1731)
    - Solomon Mykhoels Cultural Center, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 1732)
      Includes financial records
    - Struga Poetry Festival, Macedonia, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 1733)
    - UK Year of Literature and Writing, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 1734)
    - UNESCO International Round Table, "Peace, the Day After", 1993 Dec (Box 58, Folder 1735)
    - The Writer and Human Rights, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 1736)
    - Others, 1967-1999, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1737-1744)
  - PERIODICALS
    - Arabic
      - A-Sharq, 1973, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1745)
      - Al-Bilad, 1985 Mar 13 (Box 59, Folder 1746)
      - Al-Jadeed, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1747)
      - Unidentified, [1994?] (Box 59, Folder 1748)
    - Chinese
      - Foreign Literatures, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 1749)
      - Israel Magazine, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 1750)
      - Poetry, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1751)
      - Unidentified, 1993-1994 (Box 59, Folder 1752)
    - Dutch
      - Honest Arts Movement, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 1753)
      - Israel Midden-Oosten, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 1754)
      - De Jodse Wachter, [1974?] (Box 59, Folder 1755)
      - Mabat: Cultuur, Kunst en Wetenschap in Israël, 1988 Apr
      - Nieuw Wereldtudschrift, 1988, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 1756-1757)
      - De Tweede Ronde, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 1758)
      - De Vlaamse Gids, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 1759)
    - English
      - AJR Information, 1981 Oct (Box 60, Folder 1760)
      - American Poetry Review, 1973-1996
      - Anthology of Underground Poetry, 1971, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1761)
      - Ariel, 1987-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1762-1769)
      - The Atlantic, 1986 Jan (Box 60, Folder 1770)
      - The Author, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 1771)
      - Bananas, 1979
      - Book of the Month Club News, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 1772)
      - Books & Issues, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 1773)
      - Bulletin of the Israeli Academic Center in Cairo, 1988 Jul (Box 60, Folder 1774)
      - The Cleveland Jewish News, 1967 Mar 17
      - Commentary, 1967, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 1775-1776)
      - Congress Monthly, 1995 Mar (Box 60, Folder 1777)
      - Contact, 1991 Jul 26
      - Contemporary Literature in Translation (2 copies), 1968 (Box 61, Folder 1778)
      - Cross Currents, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 1779)
      - Current Biography, 1998 Feb (Box 61, Folder 1779a)
      - Diversion, 1988 May (Box 61, Folder 1780)
      - Envoy (4 copies), 1987 (Box 61, Folder 1781)
      - Eretz Magazine, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 1782)
      - Focus, 1992-1995 (Box 61, Folder 1783)
      - Forum on the Jewish People, Zionism and Israel, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 1784)
      - Free Judaism, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 1785)
      - Hadassah Magazine, 1986, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 1786-1787)
      - Harper's Magazine, 1990 Nov (Box 61, Folder 1788)
      - Hebrew Book Review, 1969, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 1789)
      - Hebrew University News, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 1790)
      - Herzl Institute Bulletin, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 1791)
      - Hungry Mind Review, 1993
      - Israel Book World, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 1792)
      - Israel Scene, 1988 Apr (Box 61, Folder 1793)
      - The Jeruslam Post, 1988, 1991
      - The Jerusalem Report, 1990-1994 (Box 61, Folder 1794)
      - Jewish Affairs, 1972 Jun (Box 61, Folder 1795)
      - Jewish Book News, 1981, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 1796-1797)
      - The Jewish Quarterly, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 1798)
      - Jewish Spectator (2 copies), 1979 (Box 62, Folder 1799)
      - Judaism, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 1800)
      - Kansas City Jewish Chronicle, 1981 Oct 9
      - Leket, 1974 Nov (Box 62, Folder 1801)
      - Lilith, 1995, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 1802)
      - The London Review of Books, 1979 Nov 22
      - Mars, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 1803)
      - Masada, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 1804)
      - The Massachusetts Review, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 1805)
      - Mishkenot Sha'ananim Newsletter, 1985-1990 (Box 62, Folder 1806)
      - Modern Hebrew Literature, 1989-1994 (Box 62, Folder 1807-1808)
      - Modern Poetry in Translation, 1965-1999 (Box 62, Folder 1809-1810)
      - Moment, 1979-1995 (Box 62, Folder 1811-1813)
      - The Nation, 1981-1982 (Box 62, Folder 1814-1815)
      - National Geographic, 1983 Apr (Box 63, Folder 1816)
      - Near Eastern Center Newsletter, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 1817)
      - The New Republic, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 1818-1819)
      - New Statesman, 1966 Feb 18 (Box 63, Folder 1820)
      - The New York Times Book Review, 1968-1986
      - The New York Times Magazine, 1986 Jun 8
      - The New Yorker, 1969-1996 (Box 63, Folder 1821-1823)
      - News from the Hebrew University of Jerusalem, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 1824)
      - News from Israel, 1993 Apr (Box 63, Folder 1825)
      - Now, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 1826)
      - Partisan Review (2 copies), 1990 (Box 63, Folder 1827-1828)
      - Poet, 1971 Mar (Box 63, Folder 1829)
      - Poetry, 1981, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 1830)
      - Poetry, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 1831)
      - Poetry Flash, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 1832)
      - Poetry New York, 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 1833)
      - Poetry Venture, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 1834)
      - Prairie Schooner, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 1835)
      - Present Tense, 1974, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 1836-1837)
      - Quarry West, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 1838)
      - Reform Judaism (3 copies), 1990 (Box 64, Folder 1839)
      - SDSU Report, 1985
      - T News, 1994 Jan
      - Tarbut, 1991, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 1840)
      - Teddy!: A Journal of Jersusalem, 1985 Nov 25 (Box 64, Folder 1841)
      - Textures, 1986 Oct (Box 64, Folder 1842)
      - Tikkun, 1996-1999 (Box 64, Folder 1843-1844)
      - The Times Literary Supplement, 1976-1988
      - The UNESCO Courrier, 1994 Oct (Box 64, Folder 1845)
      - Update, 1988 May (Box 64, Folder 1846)
      - Update, 1990, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 1847)
      - Urin v'Tumim, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 1848)
      - A View from the Loft, 1985 Jan (Box 64, Folder 1849)
      - World Literature Today, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 1850)
      - Yale Weekly Bulletin & Calendar, 1994 Oct
    - French
      - L'Arche, 1993 May (Box 64, Folder 1851)
      - Ariel, 1974, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 1852-1853)
      - Le Journal des Poètes, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 1854)
    - Georgian
      - Alioni, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 1855)
    - German
      - Allgemeine Jüdische Wochenzeitung, 1980-1981
      - Ariel, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 1856)
      - Hebräische Universität ECHO, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 1857)
      - AVS Informationsdienst, 1991 Mar (Box 65, Folder 1858)
      - Der Literatur Bote, 1992, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 1859-1860)
      - Litfass, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 1861)
      - Merian, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1862)
      - Neue Jüdische Nachrichten, 1981 Jul 3
      - Schweizer Monatshefte, 1971 Jul (Box 65, Folder 1863)
      - Tarbuton, 1994 May (Box 65, Folder 1864)
      - Trend: Magazin für Würzburg, 1992 Oct (Box 65, Folder 1865)
      - Würzburg Heute, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 1866)
    - Hebrew
      - Akhshav, 1991-1995 (Box 66, Folder 1867-1870)
      - ha-Arets, 1990, 1999
      - ha-Atid, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 1871)
      - ha-Doar, 1993 Nov 26 (Box 66, Folder 1872)
      - ha-Iyur, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1873)
      - ha-Olam ha-zeh, 1976 Jun 30 (Box 66, Folder 1874)
      - ha-Sifrût, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 1875)
      - Bor Hakeren, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 1876)
      - Ba-mahaneh, 1968-1982, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1877-1878)
      - Besha-ar, 1990 Aug 31 (Box 66, Folder 1879)
      - Big Deal, 1990 Feb 1 (Box 66, Folder 1880)
      - Daf, 1968, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 1881)
      - Egoz, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 1882)
      - Fil iton, 1976 Dec 15 (Box 67, Folder 1883)
      - Galim, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 1884)
      - Genosar, 1974 Apr 3 (Box 67, Folder 1885)
      - Hadashot Philco, 1972
      - Hotam, 1972, 1988
      - Iton, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 1886)
    - Iton 77
      - Lashon ve-Ivrit, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1887b)
      - Maariv, 1985, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 1888)
    - Mifgash
      - Miskafayim, 1993 Apr (Box 68, Folder 1890)
      - Monitin, 1985 Mar (Box 68, Folder 1891)
      - Moznayim, 1963-1990 (Box 68, Folder 1892-1898)
      - Nekudah, 1998 Apr (Box 68, Folder 1899)
      - Noar 71, 1971 Jun 1 (Box 68, Folder 1900)
      - Orot, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1901)
      - Pi ha-Aton, 1979 May 16 (Box 68, Folder 1902)
      - Proma, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1902a)
      - Rosh, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 1903)
      - Rosh 1, 1990 Jul 6 (Box 68, Folder 1904)
      - Shabat be-Shabato, 1998 May 23 (Box 68, Folder 1905)
      - Shirim, 1997 Jun (Box 68, Folder 1906)
      - Shitim, 1995 May 2 (Box 68, Folder 1907)
      - Siah Shakulim, [1987?] (Box 68, Folder 1908)
      - Siman keriah, 1973 May (Box 68, Folder 1909)
      - Skirah hadashot, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 1910)
      - Targima: du-yarhon she Agudat ha- metargemim be-Yisrael, 1989 Feb (Box 69, Folder 1911)
      - Yerushalayim Sheli, 1989 Jan 13 (Box 69, Folder 1912)
      - Yohani, [1950, 1954] (Box 69, Folder 1913)
      - Unidentified, 1993 Jun (Box 69, Folder 1914)
    - Icelandic
      - Unidentified, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 1915)
    - Italian
      - Musa, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 1916)
      - Nuovi Argomenti, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 1917)
      - Sette, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 1918)
    - Macedonian
      - Oko: Makedonska Revija za Literatura, 1995
      - Struga, 1995 Aug (Box 69, Folder 1919)
    - Romanian
      - Steaua, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 1920)
    - Russian
      - Ariel, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 1921)
      - Literaturnii Al'manakh, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 1922)
      - Rodina, 1981-1982 (Box 69, Folder 1923)
      - Uzy, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 1924)
    - [Sanskrit?]
      - Unidentified, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 1925)
    - Serbian
      - Knijzhevnost, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 1926)
    - Spanish
      - Afirmación, 1970 Feb (Box 70, Folder 1927)
      - Aqui Estamos, 1977 Sep (Box 70, Folder 1928)
      - Ariel, 1974-1988 (Box 70, Folder 1929-1930)
      - Aurora (2 copies), 1989
      - Blanco Movil, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 1931)
      - Caliartes: Revista de Artes y Letras, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 1932)
      - Comentario, 1970 May (Box 70, Folder 1933)
      - Dialogo, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 1934)
      - Juventud, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1935)
      - Letras Libres, 1999 Dec (Box 70, Folder 1936)
      - El Observador, 1992 Jun 14
      - Poesia, 1994 Nov 15 (Box 70, Folder 1937)
      - Raices, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1938)
      - Revista Ciencias de la Educacion, 1992 Apr (Box 70, Folder 1939)
        Includes letter and photograph
      - Vuelta, 1988-1995 (Box 71, Folder 1940-1942)
    - Swedish
      - Judisk Krönika, 1988 Jun (Box 71, Folder 1943)
    - Tamil
      - [Unesco Courier] translation, 1994-1995 (Box 71, Folder 1944)
  - TEACHING GUIDES
    - Batsel, rimon, ve-zayit, 1990-1991 (Box 72, Folder 1945)
    - Kriyat kayits, 1997-1998 (Box 72, Folder 1946)
    - Proyect soper-moreh be-marehet ha- hinuh, 1998 (Box 72, Folder 1947)
    - Safah ve-milim ba-shira, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 1948)
    - Tohnit limudim: tohnit limudim be-tanakh be-kitot hanhalat ha-lashot, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 1949)
  - OTHER
    - Exhibitions, 1980-1995, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1950)
    - Invitations, 1966-1999, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1951-1953)
    - Maps, 1993, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1954-1955)
    - Memorial services, 1997, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 1956)
    - Menus, 1987-1997, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1957)
    - Postcards, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1958)
    - Publicity for production of "Hair", n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1959)
    - Road atlas of North America, n.d.
    - Stamps, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1960)
    - Stationery, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1961)
    - Tickets and ticket stubs, 1982-1995, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1962)
- Audiovisual Material, 1987-1998; Series VII; 1.88; (5 boxes)
  Series VII. Audio-Visual Material, is organized into two subseries: Audio Recordings and Moving Image Material.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 99 and 100 contain audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Sound Recordings
    - Audiocassettes
      Box 98 contains audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - "Yehuda Amichai & Elizabeth Swados", 1992 November 9; 1; 00:08:00 (Box 98, Item barcode 39002099369671)
      - "Arazel: ba-historyah shel ahavatenu: 3 shirim le-tekst shel Amihai", undated; 1; 00:17:49 (Box 98, Item barcode 39002099369689)
      - "Arbeitskopi: Literatur unterwegs, Yehuda Amichai", 1988 September 22; 1; 00:51:10 (Box 98, Item barcode 39002099369697)
      - "Aval mah asita le-maan nafsheha? Kontsert En Hod", 1987 May 23; 1; 00:05:21; Program distorted at times. It is also recorded at a high level. (Box 98, Item barcode 39002099369705)
      - "B. s. le-talmide hayil, hagigat Yom Huledet", 1994; 1; 01:22:01 (Box 98, Item barcode 39002099369713)